Now, you'll notice with our edges, already sort of peeled away, you're like well, you know, some of the toners coming off, it all looks a little rugged.
First off, some of the rugged, harder edged effects, that is part of the transfer.
You gotta keep in mind that a lot of those with smoother edges, that the grays and the whites are going to be reduced down to like, you know, darker than wood.
What's more, if you discover, if you think too much toner's coming off, to the point where you're losing the image, odds are you're scrubbing too hard.
Go from the rough side, to the smooth side.
What's more, in terms of getting into, like, the really more detailed areas, where you're just going to be on the basic shape of the shoulder.
I strong, strongly recommend just rubbing with the smooth side, and having a lot of water, cause this is going to help you, get even more of the paper off.
And you'll notice that, you know, a lot of the toner underneath here, is staying on, much more so, than what you had on, lower below.
But yeah, if you find out that a lot of it's coming off, stop scrubbing so hard.
That's probably the big problem.
Cause, yeah, some of the toner will come off, that's part again, part of, sort of part of the effect, but you should still be able to very easily recognize the picture underneath.
And you shouldn't be taking off big heaps of toner.
That means you are scrubbing too hard.
So, with the smooth side, we're going to work in here, all through out the middle, until we have all the paper, that we want all the paper fiber, is going to be off.